http://www.dond.co.uk/privacy.php

Your Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this
notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make
about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy
to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where
personally identifiable information may be requested.
Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on
this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to
visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites
on the internet.
To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content
network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s
own privacy policies.
Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to
track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness
and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, www.dond.co.uk
has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party
advertisers.
Collection of Personal Information
When visiting www.dond.co.uk, the IP address used to access the site will be
logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely
used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather
broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded
IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Links to third party Websites
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not
responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware
that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.
Changes to this Privacy Statement
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.
If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of www.dond.co.uk
then you may contact us at admin@dond.co.uk
Copyright ©2006-2011 dond.co.uk - All rights reserved. www.dond.co.uk is NOT the official website of Deal or No Deal
This site www.dond.co.uk is NOT connected in any way, commercial or otherwise to Endemol or Channel 4 or their respective websites.
Computer repair Redruth |
Actifry KW Autos | Deal or No Deal Online Games | Onesie | Websites Cornwall | Innotab 2 | Iphone repair | DJ Cornwall | Monkeygamer | Monkeygamer Youtube |
